

#### Hanyang University · Chungbuk Science High sch

Seongdong-gu, Seoul, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-3033-5590 | **≥** kyaryunha@naver.com | **⊙** kyaryunha

"I want to be a Great Programmer! Can you help me?"

# **Summary**

I'm a freshman in college and currently pursuing a Bachelor of Science in computer software engineering
I learned C in high school as my first programming language; and found out that I loved algorithmic problem solving.

After the finish university entrance examination, I began to study Web Front End, and It's my first development experience.

When I became a university student, I start studying TeX, 3D Printing, Python, Object Detection(but I don't know ML, just use Tensorflow API).

## Education

Hanyang University Seoul, S.Kored

COMPUTER SOFTWARE Mar. 2019

• 222, Wangsimni-ro, Seongdong-gu, Seoul, 04763, Korea

### Skills

**Programming Language** C, C++, TeX, Python, JavaScript

Web Front-End HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

**3D Printing** Fusion 360

**Illustration** Clip Studio, Photoshop

**Development Tools** Github, CodeBlocks, VS Code, Atom, Pycharm, TeX Studio, Overleaf

Try a little Kotlin, Aheui(아희), Jetson Nano, Object Detection

**Others** Data Structure, Algorithm

#### Awards

#### **ALGORITHM**

2016	Encouragement Prize(167th), KOI(Korean Olympiad in Informatics)	KIISE
2016	Excellence Prize Prize(6th), National High School Girl Programming Contest	Ewha Womans Univ
2017	Silver Prize(29th), KOI(Korean Olympiad in Informatics)	KIISE
2017	Finalist, NEXON Youth Programming Challenge	NEXON
2018	Asia 308th, Kor 23rd, Asia Pacific Information Olympiad	Innopolis
2018	Finalist, NEXON Youth Programming Challenge	NEXON
2019	27th, UCPC(National College Student Programming Contest)	UCPC
2019	23place(50th), ICPC Seoul Regional	ICPC

## **Presentation**

### T<sub>E</sub>X Book Design: Page styles and Title

Kongju, S.Korea

Nov. 2019

THE KOREAN TEX SOCIETY WORKSHOP

- Introduce about how design pagestyles using T<sub>F</sub>X's package memoir
- Translation and summary about Madsen's pagestyles manual.
- Introduce about my document design using memoir
- http://wiki.ktug.org/wiki/wiki.php/LaTeXWorkshop/2019

# **Work Experience**

#### Try to Solve 4x4x4 Magic Cube Using Simulated Annealing

Cheongju, S.Kored

2018 CHUNGBUK SCIENCE HIGH SCHOOL MATH MAGAZINE

Mar.2018 - Apr. 2018

- Magic Cube is a number from 1 to 64 arranged in a cube-like arrangement so that the sum of 76 horizontal, vertical, and diagonal segments is equal.
- Way to arrange 64 in a cube with about  $10^{18}$
- · Finding an array that satisfies about 38 segments in about 9 seconds using the Simulated Annealing technique

My Site Cheongju, S.Korec

FIRST WEB FRONT END WORK

Sep. 2018 - Oct. 2018

- · HTML, CSS, Javascript
- 1. Sleep Computer(Fill the screen with the desired color)
- 2. Arithmetic Sequence Game(Play 7\*7 Arithmetic Sequence game, This game made by me.)
- kyaryunha.com

**Draw Graph**Cheongju, S.Korec

SECOND WEB FRONT END WORK

Nov. 2018

- Click for draw the vertices and edges of the graph
- · HTML, CSS, Javascript
- · Custom vertices and edges of different shapes, colors, and sizes
- · kyaryunha.com/drawgraph

Christmas Tree Cheongiu, S.Kored

THIRD WEB FRONT END WORK

Dec. 2018

- Draw Christmas Tree (Forest)
- · HTML, CSS, Javascript
- · Edges directly connected to the root are colored brown, and edges not associated with the root are colored green
- Restricts drawing of non-tree(forest) graphs
- When MST mode is activated, Minimum Spanning Tree is automatically calculated
- kyaryunha.com/christmas

3D Printing Seoul, S.Korea

HANYANG UNIV ENGINEERING ACADEMIC CLUB BARAMI, HANYANG ACADEMIC TOWN PROGRAM

Mar. 2019 - Apr. 2019

- Studying 3D Modeling, Simulation, and Rapid Prototyping Using Fusion 360 and Assembling 3D Printer Prusa MK3
- Producing by modeling some necessary parts in the club

Catch Catch Seoul, S.Korea

SOFTWARE MAESTRO 10TH, TEAM.CATCH CATCH

Jun. 2019 - Nov. 2019

- Digital media interactive content for pets
   Real Time Object Detection Cat and Dog using Haar Cas
- · Real Time Object Detection Cat and Dog using Haar Cascade, Mask RCNN, YOLO(Darknet), mobilenetSSD(Caffe, Tensorflow) on Windows
- Collect Image Data about Cat Top View
- Labeling and Training Cat, Cat's head, Cat's paw at mobilenetSSD(Tensorflow)
- · Real Time Object Detection Cat, Cat's head, Cat's paw using mobilenetSSD(Tensorflow) on Windows
- Real Time Object Detection Cat and Dog using mobilenetSSD(TensorRT), Yolo(Darknet, TensorRT), Tiny Yolo(Darknet) on Jetson Nano
- Printing product case made with Fusion360

# **School Activity**

## Hanyang Univ Engineering Academic Club BARAMI

Seoul, S.Korea Mar. 2019 - PRESENT

MEMBER (MAR. 2019), VICE-PRESIDENT (DEC. 2019)

- Electrical and Bio-Engineering, Electronic Engineering, Computer Software's club
- Hold and take long-term and short-term seminars
- · Exhibition of works in November every year
- Dec. 2019, Be elected Vice-President

DECEMBER 13, 2019 SHIN HYUN · CV